Guide to the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), Pittsburgh Branch Records, 1940-1974 AIS.1964.38
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- 1960-1961
  - Correspondence from National Office, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 11-13)
  - Correspondence to National Office, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 1-8)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
  - Current Bills, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Education, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - F.E.P.C., 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Finance Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Health and Welfare Federation, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Housing, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Human Rights Dinner, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Community Relations Council, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Religious and Civic Organizations, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous notes, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Memberships, Life, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Membership Campaign, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Members not received, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 5-6)
  - NAACP College Chapter, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Intergroup relations - Annual Meeting, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - National Office, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - News Releases - Courier, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - News Releases - National, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 11-13)
  - Paid Bills, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
  - Pennsylvania Equal Rights Council, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Periodicals and Circulars, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 2-5)
  - Persons Seeking Employment, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 6-7)
  - Photos - Group, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Presbyterian Magazine, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Local Press Releases, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Prospective Office Machines, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Program File, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Public Accommodations Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Radio Transcripts, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 6-7)
  - Solicitation Information, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Solicitation License, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - State Conference, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Trend Magazine, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Washington Bureau, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Women's Auxiliary, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Y.W.C.A., 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Youth Council, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- 1962
  - Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Biographical Materials - Jack Greenberg, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Catholic Interracial Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 19-22)
  - Correspondence from National Office, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
  - Complaints, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Directories, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Employment Applications, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 7-10)
  - Employment Committee, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Housing Committee, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Human Relations Committee, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 13-14)
  - Labor and Industrial Committee Correspondence, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Labor and Industrial Committee Correspondence, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Labor and Industrial Committee, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Local Board Material, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Membership, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Membership Campaign, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Membership, Life, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous notes, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - News Releases - Courier, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - News Releases - Local, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Prospects for 1962 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Paid Bills, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 13-14)
  - Pennsylvania Equal Rights Council, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Office Supplies - Advertising, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Committee, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Prospective Machines, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Periodicals and Circulars, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Radio Transcripts - WDKA, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Radio Transcripts - WAMO, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Receipts - National Office, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Solicitation Taxes, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - State Conferences, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Telegrams, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Post Office, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Urban League, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Weirton Steel Company, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Young Adults, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- 1963
  - Applications, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Catholic Interracial Council, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Centennial Rally, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Commission on Human Rights, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Contributions, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from National Office, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 2-4)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 5-8)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to National Office, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Critics, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Directories, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Educational Committee, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Emancipation Proclamation, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Executive Secretary, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Grisby Case, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Human Rights Dinner, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 9-11)
  - Jobs Available, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - KDKA, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Life Membership, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Local Branch, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - March on Washington, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Reports, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Labor and Industry, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - NAACP, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - National Office, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - News Letters, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
  - News Releases, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Paid Bills, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 9-10)
  - Pamphlets, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania Commission on Human Rights, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania State Conference, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Personnel Department, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Public Relations, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Radio Stations, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Solicitation License, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Special Projects, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Urban League, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Washington, D.C. Correspondence - Incoming, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - WAMO, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Herb Wilkerson, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 12-13)
  - Women's Auxiliary, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Western Union, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - YMCA, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Youth Divisions, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Postmaster of Pittsburgh, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Pamphlets, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 19-20)
- 1965
  - Correspondence, General Incoming, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 1-3)
  - Correspondence, National Office - Incoming, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, National Office - Outgoing, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Justin Obi, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Telegrams, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Church Work Committee, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Education Committee, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Education Committee, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Committee, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Housing Committee, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Labor and Industry Committee, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Membership Committee, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Voter Registration Committee, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Women's Auxiliary, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Youth Council, Jr. Youth Council, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Budget and Finance, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Contributions, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Financial Reports, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Report to National Office on Receipts, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Paid Bills, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Taxes - Federal, City, School, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Membership, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Life Membership, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Action Files, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 4-6)
  - Alphonso G. Roberts, Jr., 1965 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Complaint Forms, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Freedom Rally, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Leadership Action Committee on Civil Rights (Formerly Western Pa. March on Washington), 1965 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Special Projects (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - War on Poverty (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Allegheny Union Baptist (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Business and Job Development Corporation, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Chartiers Valley NAACP, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - COFO, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Education Fund (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Commission on Human Relations (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania State Conference, NAACP, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Wilkinsburg Unit, NAACP (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Directories (Box 54, Folder 8)
- 1966
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence, National Office, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 11-12)
  - Executive Board, 1966; II (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Education Committee, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Housing Committee, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Press Publicity Committee, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Reports to National Office on Receipts, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Paid Bills, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Membership, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Life Members, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Complaints, Action Files, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Complaints, Turner-Taylor, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Special Projects, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
  - Chartiers Valley, NAACP, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania State Conference, NAACP (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - United Negro Protest Committee, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Youth Council, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- NAACP Reports
  - Annual Report, Pittsburgh Branch, NAACP, 1971-1974 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
  - Annual Report, Pittsburgh Branch, NAACP, Counseling, Coordination and Placement Bureau, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Stevens, Tim. "Urban Community Development and Placement: the Pittsburgh NAACP", 1973 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- NAACP, Membership Return Envelopes
  - 1956 (Box 58)
  - 1957 (Box 59)
  - 1958 (Box 60)
  - 1959 (Box 61)
  - 1961 (Box 62)